Create Your DRF Account

New to DRF?

Everything you could possibly  
need in one place

Register

Don't have an account? Register Here

DRF PRIVACY POLICY
------------------

Effective: May 9, 2024

Sports Information Group, LLC, and it subsidiaries, including Daily Racing Form LLC (collectively, "DRF" or "We" or "Us"), which is a subsidiary of Affinity Interactive, takes your privacy very seriously. Please carefully read this Privacy Policy and familiarize yourself with our privacy practices regarding your personal information and how we will use it. This Privacy Policy applies to the DRF site, including mobile sites or apps (collectively, the "Sites"). By visiting the Sites, you accept this Privacy Policy and DRF's Web Site Subscriber Agreement, which are hereby incorporated. If you do not agree with these policies, do not use the Sites.

In this Privacy Policy, we cover:

* Notice at collection
* Information we collect
* How we collect information
* How we use your information
* Disclosure of Information
* Research
* Your U.S. State Privacy Rights
* Third Party Web Sites
* Security
* Children
* Data Controller, Data Protection Officer
* Changes and Updates
* Contact Us

**I. Notice at collection**

Below is a summary of the categories of personal information we collect and how we use that information.

| Personal Information We Collect | How We Use Your Personal Information |
| --- | --- |
| identifiers and contact information | To enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions;  <br>To alert you to new projects, Sites features, special events and services;  <br>To conduct surveys to measure your satisfaction with our service;  <br>To enforce DRF's rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and DRF;  <br>To protect DRF’s rights or property or the safety of DRF, our members, or others;  <br>To comply with any court order, legal process, or respond to any governmental or regulatory request;  <br>To transfer information in the event of a merger, transfer of assets or other organizational restructuring;  <br>To advertise and market our Sites, products, and services and/or third party Web sites, products, and services. |
| payment information | To enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions;  <br>To enforce DRF's rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and DRF;  <br>To protect DRF’s rights or property or the safety of DRF, our members, or others;  <br>To comply with any court order, legal process, or respond to any governmental or regulatory request;  <br>To transfer information in the event of a merger, transfer of assets or other organizational restructuring. |
| demographic information | To conduct surveys to measure your satisfaction with our service;  <br>To enforce DRF's rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and DRF;  <br>To protect DRF’s rights or property or the safety of DRF, our members, or others;  <br>To comply with any court order, legal process, or respond to any governmental or regulatory request;  <br>To transfer information in the event of a merger, transfer of assets or other organizational restructuring;  <br>To advertise and market our Sites, products, and services and/or third party Web sites, products, and services. |
| network activity information | We sell or share information about your internet and network activity with third parties for targeted advertisements on and off of our Services. <br><br>We also use this information:  <br>To enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions;  <br>To alert you to new projects, Sites features, special events and services;  <br>To conduct surveys to measure your satisfaction with our service;  <br>To enforce DRF's rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and DRF;  <br>To protect DRF’s rights or property or the safety of DRF, our members, or others;  <br>To comply with any court order, legal process, or respond to any governmental or regulatory request;  <br>To transfer information in the event of a merger, transfer of assets or other organizational restructuring;  <br>To monitor and evaluate our Sites and identify where we should make changes or expand services;  <br>To advertise and market our Sites, products, and services and/or third party Web sites, products, and services. |
| inferences | We sell or share inferences with third parties for targeted advertisements on and off of our Services. <br><br>We also use this information:  <br>To enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions;  <br>To alert you to new projects, Sites features, special events and services;  <br>To conduct surveys to measure your satisfaction with our service;  <br>To comply with any court order, legal process, or respond to any governmental or regulatory request;  <br>To transfer information in the event of a merger, transfer of assets or other organizational restructuring;  <br>To monitor and evaluate our Sites and identify where we should make changes or expand services;  <br>To advertise and market our Sites, products, and services and/or third party Web sites, products, and services. |
| job applicant information | For general business operations;  <br>To protect our rights or property or our safety, our members, or others; |

We do not use any sensitive personal information for any purpose outside of the purpose for which it was shared with us.

We will retain your personal information for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes described above. Please see the Your U.S. State Privacy Rights section of this Privacy Policy for information about your rights pursuant to applicable California law.

**Information we collect**

We use YouTube API Services and by agreeing to our policies you are also agreeing to [YouTube's Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms) and [Google Privacy Policy.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy)

You may be asked to provide:

• identifiers, such as your name, as well as the last four digits of your Social Security number (which is for identity verification purposes only);

• contact information like your email address, mailing address, or phone number; 

• payment information, such as such as credit card information and banking and personal credit information

• Precise geolocation information, including your precise GPS location when you access our Services, or when your Wi-Fi or Bluetooth-enabled device connects to, or is detected by, the wireless networks at certain properties (including when our app is closed or not in use);

demographic information, if you choose to provide it, like your gender and age; and/or

• inferences about you and your interests and personal preferences;

• job applicant information, such as job history, qualifications and other information stated on the resume or job history submitted by the applicant

When using our Sites, we also collect Internet or other electronic network activity information. When you use the Internet, your web browser or client software may transmit certain information to the servers that host the Web sites you visit. This Internet and other electronic network activity information (“Network Activity Information”) may include the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, the capabilities and features of your computer, your geographic location, and your movement within and interaction with the Web site, including what pages you look at and what information you download. 

**How we collect information**

We collect and obtain personal information at various points throughout the Sites, including from our subscribers during the free membership registration process, paid subscription process and, occasionally, at other times. This information, which ranges from limited personal information such as age and address to facts about subscribers' computers, professions and leisure habits, is then securely stored on separate servers. Specifically, our sources of personal information include:

You. We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us, for example if you decide to register an account, place a bet, sign up for our rewards program, shop through the Sites, subscribe to a service, or otherwise request a product/service or actively engage with the Sites. 

**Service Providers.** DRF may use third-party service providers or other third party organizations helping to support our mission that may collect, store, or process your personal information on DRF’s behalf, such as to complete your request, e.g. completing a transaction or to outsource one or more of the functions described above. 

**Third-Party Advertisers.** We work with companies that help us deliver, measure, and analyze the effectiveness of our ads. These companies collect information about you when you interact with ads on our platforms and on the

**Cookie Technology.** We employ cookie technology to help subscribers move faster through our Site. When a consumer visits our Site or subscriber signs on to DRF Online, we pass several cookies to that user's computer. A cookie is a string of information that's sent by a Web site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. This avoids the potentially time-consuming task of checking our registration database each time a page is requested. The cookie is deleted when a user chooses the log out feature to terminate their session. We also employ cookie technology to store subscribers' User Names and Passwords. Read our cookie disclosure statement and view a cookie-by-cookie breakdown.

**Other Sources.** We may also obtain information about you from other sources, including publicly available sources.

**How we use information**

Personal information may be used in several ways:

• To enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions;

• To alert you to new projects, Sites features, special events and services;

• To conduct surveys to measure your satisfaction with our service;

• To enforce DRF's rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and DRF;

• To protect DRF’s rights or property or the safety of DRF, our members, or others;

• To comply with any court order, legal process, or respond to any governmental or regulatory request;

• To transfer information in the event of a merger, transfer of assets or other organizational restructuring;

• To monitor and evaluate our Sites and identify where we should make changes or expand services;

• To provide advertisers with information that does not directly identify you (e.g. aggregate information about our subscriber base and usage patterns) ;

• To give DRF's marketing and development staff information that's useful for developing new features and services that meet subscriber needs;

• To share data with our affiliated companies for joint marketing and other purposes; and

• To share data with nonaffiliated third parties who provide products and services that may be of 1.5. 

Additionally, we may receive, collect or use your precise geolocation information for advertising purposes and to look at your visits to various properties. You can manage access to precise geolocation information at any time in your device settings.

**Disclosure of information**

DRF may use third-party service providers or other third party organizations helping to support our mission that may collect, store, or process your personal information on DRF’s behalf, such as to complete your request, e.g. completing a transaction or to outsource one or more of the functions described above.

Specifically, we will share your personal information with the following categories of third parties:

**Our affiliate companies**;, for purposes of fulfilling an order or other request, or jointly marketing products/services;

**Our service providers**, which are companies and individuals that provide services on our behalf or help us operate the our Sites or our business. For example, we share your payment information with third party service providers for purposes of processing your payment for products and services that you purchase. We also share personal information with third party analytics companies that help us to monitor traffic on the Sites, learn how users are navigating our Sites, and help troubleshoot or improve the services we provide.

Our **business partners**, which are non-affiliated third parties who provide products/services that may be of interest to you.

**Third-party advertising partners** to serve ads when you visit our Sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

**Law enforcement or legal authorities**, in response to lawfully served process or subpoena. Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personal information. We will disclose personal information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, warrant, or other legal process to the extent necessary to meet legal, national security, public interest, or law enforcement obligations. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our Services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful;

**Successor company or companies** in the event that DRF ceases operations for any reason. In the event that we enter into an agreement to be purchased by another company or to merge with another company, we may share personal information with that company. We will require that such purchasers continue to comply with the provisions as outlined in this Privacy Policy;

**Market-research firms**, as more fully described below.

**Research**

We may contract with a market-research firm to conduct occasional online surveys. When you're within DRF Online, you may see a pop-up window offering you the optional opportunity of participating in a survey. If you do not wish to participate, simply click the "No, Thank You" link and you will not see this window again. If you choose to participate, you'll be prompted to answer a series of online questions. You will be prompted to enter your e-mail address for validation purposes but no other personal information (name, address, etc.) will be collected as part of the survey. In some cases, however, you may be offered a free gift for your participation. We will need your name and address, which will be used exclusively to fulfill your gift request.

Your Choices

**Opt out of email marketing communications**. To stop receiving marketing emails, use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each message or email us at [cservice2@drf.com](mailto:cservice2@drf.com). Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions.

**Opt out of cookies and similar technologies**. We and our service providers, advertisers, and other third parties use cookies and similar technologies to recognize you on and off our Services. For more information about the use of cookies and similar technologies on the Services (including your opt-out choices) please see our [Cookie Disclosure Statement.](https://www.drf.com/about_cookie)

**Your [U.S. State Privacy Rights](https://www.drf.com/CCPA)**

If you are resident of certain states in the U.S., you may have additional choices and rights regarding your personal information. Some of these choices and rights vary based on where you live. For additional information about your choices and rights under certain U.S. state privacy laws, please visit this [link.](https://www.burton.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-Burton_NA-Site/en_US/Page-Show?cid=your-california-privacy-rights)

**Third Party Web Sites**

Our Sites may contain links to other Web sites provided by third parties.  Please be aware that we do not control these third party Web sites or any of the content contained on those Web sites.  Once you have left our Sites, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of such other Web sites.  We encourage you to exercise caution and to read the privacy policy for the Web site you visit.  The inclusion of hyperlinks to third party Web sites on our Sites in no way constitutes an endorsement by us of such Web sites' content, actions or policies.

**Security**

DRF is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and takes steps to help protect the personal information you provide to us. However, no transmission or electronic storage of information is guaranteed to be secure. We therefore urge you to always use caution when transmitting information over the Internet.

**Children**

The Sites are not directed toward children under 18 years of age nor does DRF knowingly collect information from children under 18.  If you are under 18, please do not use the Sites or submit any personally identifiable information to DRF.

**Data Controller, Data Protection Officer**

The Daily Racing Form is responsible for your privacy protection and is the official service provider.  If you have questions regarding our Sites, the following information, or if you would like to contact our privacy protection representative, please contact us at [cservice2@drf.com](mailto:cservice2@drf.com).

When you use our Sites, we share information that we collect from you, such as your email (in hashed form), IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with our partner/service provider, LiveRamp Inc. LiveRamp returns an online identification code that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online and cross-channel advertising and it may be shared with advertising companies to enable interest-based and targeted advertising. To opt out of this use, please click here

**Changes and Updates**

DRF may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes on this page and update the date at the top, so be sure to check back periodically to stay aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the Sites after changes have been posted will constitute your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any changes.

**International Visitors**

We store and process your data in the United States, and we intend our services only to be used in the United States. If you are located in a foreign jurisdiction and do not want to transfer your data to the United States or if it is illegal to transfer or process your data in the United States, please do not use our services.

**Contact Us**

We are located at:

Daily Racing Form

155 E44th Street,

New York, NY, 10017

If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, or to update any information you have provided us, please send us an e-mail at [cservice2@drf.com](mailto:cservice2@drf.com).

**Your U.S. State Privacy Rights Privacy Rights**

You have the following rights, where provided under applicable state law, regarding your personal information (each of which are subject to various exceptions and limitations):

Right of Access. You have the right to access your personal information maintained by us. Upon receipt of a verifiable request to access personal information, we will disclose and deliver, free of charge, the personal information requested.

Please note that we are not required to provide personal information to you more than twice in a 12-month period.

_Right of Correction. You have the right to request that we correct inaccurate personal information collected from you._ 

_Right of Deletion._ You have the right to request that we delete any personal information about you which we have collected from you. Upon receipt of a verifiable request for deletion, we will delete your personal information from our records and direct any service providers to delete your personal information from our records, within 45 days.

We will comply with your request to delete personal information unless it is necessary for us to maintain your personal information in order to:

• Complete a transaction, provide requested-for goods/services, and/or perform a contract between you and us;

• Detect security incidents;

• Comply with a legal obligation;

• Enable our internal uses that are aligned with your expectations and your relationship with us.

Submission of Requests for Deletion. We have designated the following methods to submit requests for deletion: (1) By submitting a request via [cservice2@drf.com](mailto:cservice2@drf.com), or (2) By calling 1-(800) 306-FORM (3676)? 

After you submit a request, we will promptly take steps to determine whether your request is a verifiable request. We will verify that you are who you say you are by:

Having you log-in through your password-protected account; or.

Having you provide unique information relating to a recent transaction or order.

We will delete your personal information to you free of charge within 45 days of receiving your verifiable request. If necessary, we will extend the time period by an additional 45 days, and will provide you with notice of the extension within the first 45-day period. 

_Right to Opt Out (Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information_). You have the right to opt-out of the “sale” of your personal information (defined very broadly to include situations where we provide personal information to partners who provide advertising services to us) and the “sharing” of personal information in connection with the display of targeted advertising across third party Web sites. You can direct us not to sell or share your personal information by submitting an opt-out request through the link “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information” which can be accessed at the bottom of our Site, or by contacting us at [cservice2@drf.com](mailto:cservice2@drf.com). We also honor the Global Privacy Control, a browser-based opt-out signal. We do not respond to other browser-based signals that do not meet applicable state law requirements, which may include older Do Not Track signals.

Right to Appeal. You have a right to appeal decisions concerning your ability to exercise your consumer rights.  

Submission of Requests for Information. We have designated the following methods for California residents to submit requests for information:

• By using your password-protected account and going to the [Member Update](https://registration.drf.com/member-update) page;

• By submitting a request via [cservice2@drf.com](mailto:cservice2@drf.com);

• By calling 1-(800) 306-FORM (3676)

Verification. After you submit a request, we will promptly take steps to determine whether your request is a verifiable request. We will verify that you are who you say you are by:

• Having you log-in through your password-protected account; or.

• Having you provide unique information relating to a recent transaction or order.

We will disclose and deliver the required information to you free of charge within 45 days of receiving your verifiable request. If necessary, we will extend the time period to provide the required information once by an additional 45 days, and will provide you with notice of the extension within the first 45-day period. 

As noted below, we do not knowingly collect information from or about children, including children aged 18 and under. We do not sell information of minors under 18 years of age.

Authorized Agent. You have the right to designate an authorized agent to submit an access or deletion request on your behalf. If you use an authorized agent to submit such a request, we will require that you:

• Provide the authorized agent written permission to act on your behalf; and

• Verify your own identity with us before we can honor the request.

No Discrimination. We will not discriminate against a California resident because the California resident exercised any of the rights described here.

**Additional Information for California Users**

• _Notice of Financial Incentive_.  As part of our services, there will be opportunities to participate in surveys and rewards programs. If you choose to participate in a survey or a rewards program, we may offer you coupons, discounts, or other promotions (e.g. enhanced stays and special benefits at our property). Such offers may not be available at all times. The amount and terms of such offers will be presented to you at the time of the offer. You can terminate your participation in these offers using the rights described in this Privacy Policy. Our good faith estimate of the value of your personal information is the value of the benefit we offer to you. We have calculated such value by using the expense related to the benefit.

_Shine the Light_. California’s “Shine The Light” law permits California residents to annually request and obtain information free of charge about what personal information is disclosed to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year.

DRF.com News Search

 Horse/Trainer/Jockey name

* Horse Racing Events
* Horse Racing News
* Tracks
* Handicapping & PPs

Get our free Newsletter, DRF Morning Line

Free Race-of-the-Day video analysis & PPs, DRF Bets Gameplan Play-of-the-Day, all the latest racing news and more.

Sign Up for Newsletter

© 2024 Daily Racing Form. All rights reserved

Download DRF Bets on your smartphone

Don't miss the break! Follow DRF

© 2024 Daily Racing Form. All rights reserved
